Hello guys, welcome to another video of stock
market.  Friends, the
March quarter results of ICICI LBA General Insurance have been
released, which is the audited
financial results.  Third
fourth quarter of financial year ended
which we will cover in this video today.
Let's start the video friends.
And guys, we will cover the
consolidated results.  Along with this,
final dividend of equity share has also been
recommended at ₹7.  It will be approved in the upcoming meeting.
So let's move on to the results
and cover the consolidated results.
Talking about the numbers, if we look at the numbers given, then the
premium earned this time in lax, if we look at the
net return, the premium earned is Rs
5790 crores, last quarter Rs 5685
crores, last quarter Rs 525 crores, premium earned increased
quarter on quarter and year on year
in both, but here the
investment income was Rs 796 crores, other
income was Rs 31 crores, after which the total income
was Rs 668 crores, last one is Rs 6610 crores, the
total income is Rs 5800 51 crores.   There was
minor growth quarter on quarter.
What is Reason?  Investment income which has been
reduced significantly this time.  But it has increased year on
year.
This time the company's expense is around Rs 673 crore.  Last of Rs
639 crore.  Last year, the expenditure was Rs 5435 crore.
Expenses also
increased quarter on quarter and year on year
according to the income.  But the profit has come out
but the expenses have
increased quarter on quarter
and here the investment income is less
due to which there has been a slight decline in the profit.
Talking about operating profit, the operating
sorority net profit which is ₹546 crore
last quarter is ₹658 crore and last quarter profit is ₹59
crore.  It is down quarter on
quarter but has increased year on year.
And if we talk about the
EPS of Guys Company, then it is down from ₹10.9
in the last quarter to ₹1.1 in the last year and
₹1.2 in the quarter on quarter and has
increased year on year.  So
if we look at the results of the company, if we
look at the
results of this time, there
is growth in income but due to investment income, the
profit of the company has been seen going down.
Now here if we talk about the
solvency ratio of Guys Company, it
is 2.67%, which is seen to be reducing slightly in the last 2.7%.
So the overall result is fine, the
profit down quarter on
quarter can impact the share in this way.
Now look at the net
premium earned by the company, if we look at it,
here the company has seen a year-on-year increase of 10.8%,
mainly the
premium earned is
important and the investment income
depends on the return on the investment it makes in the market, this time the market
condition was a bit bad, due to which the company's
numbers went down from the last quarter, now
if we look here, apart from this, the
profit increased by 7.3% and a dividend of ₹7 was
also paid, it has been recommended that it should be
approved in the upcoming meeting, so
looking at the results, good
results have been seen.  The stock closed at ₹1864.
Profit is 4.6%.  If seen in five days, there
is 6.6% profit.
If we look at it approximately in 1 month, there is a profit of 0.7%.
So guys let's end the video here.
If you have any doubt, ask in the comment box.
See you in the next video.
Bye-bye.